<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>jsyang.ca</title>
    <link>http://jsyang.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on jsyang.ca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jsyang.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Think Outside Bluetooth Folding Keyboard</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/think-outside-bluetooth-folding-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/think-outside-bluetooth-folding-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>When the local coronavirus restrictions were enacted early on this year, I was determined not to let this time go to waste. The idea: read more and improve my writing by removing distractions where possible. Distraction-free writing (post coming soon) and other activities of this sort require a lot of forethought and set-up to have a chance at consistent success.
With respect to that, one area I started to consider was the hardware: what would I use to write?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How different languages sing Happy Birthday</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/culture/how-different-languages-sing-happy-birthday/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/culture/how-different-languages-sing-happy-birthday/</guid>
      <description>The end of year winter season is a time when many of my family and friends celebrate their birthdays. This year I came across a Cantonese birthday song beyond the basic &amp;ldquo;happy birthday&amp;rdquo; / 生日快樂 that made me ponder whether other such &amp;ldquo;folk&amp;rdquo; birthday songs existed.
What are people singing about when they sing a common happy birthday song in their own language?
Let&amp;rsquo;s start with the baseline:
English Happy birthday to you Happy birthday to you Happy birthday dear &amp;lt;NAME&amp;gt; Happy birthday to you  Origin: an American children&amp;rsquo;s 1911 songbook derived from various earlier works going back to 1850s, possibly further.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WormForm - a Typography Block Sandbox</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/wormform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/wormform/</guid>
      <description>The name comes from the first thing I tried to recreate within it: the NASA worm logo.
There&amp;rsquo;s a Twitter account I follow which often posts design-related inspiration and imagery from various books, artists, and commercial products: @presentcorrect. I happened upon a post that caught my eye. It was this page from the Gujarati Type Foundry Book (1940):
I knew I had to put something together to play with this system that laid out as pieces of multi-language typefaces with simple geometric shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dahon PrestoLite - The Lightest 16&#34; Wheeler Yet</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-prestolite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-prestolite/</guid>
      <description>The Dahon PrestoLite is a 16&amp;rdquo; (ETRTO 305mm) wheeled folding bike with the geometry of a Moulton Mk3 constructed mainly out of aluminium. I&amp;rsquo;ve lusted after a Moulton Mk3 for a while but the small apartment where we live didn&amp;rsquo;t have the storage space for yet another non-folding bike; regardless of how small the wheels were.
  0th
      1st
      2nd</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Palm PVG100 phone on Three UK</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/tiny-palm-pvg100-phone-on-three-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/tiny-palm-pvg100-phone-on-three-uk/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve always favored peculiarly sized versions of everyday things (for instance, my small-wheel bike obsessions), so when Verizon paired with TCL to release a tiny 3.3 inch Android &amp;ldquo;companion&amp;rdquo; phone in November 2018, I kept a close watch on where I might be able to source one of these. Manufactured by TCL, it retains the &amp;ldquo;Palm&amp;rdquo; brand that people remember from the by-gone PDA days.
Originally the concept of the phone was as a kind of &amp;ldquo;gig&amp;rdquo; device where you would install a SIM card that kept the same phone number as your main phone but was small enough to take with you to an event where you could use a compact version of your main phone (with the majority of its features) in a pinch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guitar Hero Live Bluetooth controller</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/ghliveble/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/ghliveble/</guid>
      <description>Ever since we visited the National Videogame Museum, my wife and I got more and more into Guitar Hero style rhythm games. Late last year, I did some research and found a great open source project called Clone Hero which aims to vastly improve upon games of this genre.
For her birthday, I got an XBox360 version of the Guitar Hero Live controller which is meant to work with Windows PCs though with a steps of complicated set up before we could play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jersey on a Pacific CarryMe</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/jersey-on-a-pacific-carryme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/jersey-on-a-pacific-carryme/</guid>
      <description>Jersey the Channel Island Jersey is the largest of the Channel Islands, located in the English Channel between England and France (but closer to France). As a dependency, but not formally a part of the United Kingdom, it has a mix of British and French cultures. With both English, and French being official languages, it was the only place outside of Canada I&amp;rsquo;ve travelled to with this specific combination of dual language road signage!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific CarryMe Shakedown Cruise</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme-shakedown-cruise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme-shakedown-cruise/</guid>
      <description>The Chorlton Wanderers are a local social cycling group riding out of Chorlton Water Park, who do a social ride once a month. Given that the August 2019 ride was relatively flat and short (~60km), I decided to attempt it on the Pacific CarryMe to see what riding it for more than 10km was like in terms of pacing, fit, and to generally gauge the fun level.
It was the first shakedown cruise of the Pacific CarryMe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ender 3 Configuration Notes</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/3dprinting/ender-3-mods/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/3dprinting/ender-3-mods/</guid>
      <description>What follows is a collection of notes I compiled for setting up my current (as of 2019) 3D printer. Table of contents for major sections as follows:
1. Costs 2. Subtractive modifications 3. Printable mods 4. Octoprint 5. `mjpg-streamer` tweaks 6. Raspbian tweaks 7. G-Code tweaks  1. Costs 1 x Ender 3: £176
 50% cheaper vs previous 3D printer (Wanhao Duplicator i3 plus): £339  1 x Raspberry Pi Zero W: £18</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific CarryMe Folding Bike</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme/</guid>
      <description>The CarryMe is a folding bike with an incredibly small wheel size of 8 inches manufactured by Pacific Cycles. The main advantage is its folding style which seeks to balance a stick-shaped fold while maintaining the ergonomics of a regular bike.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been dreaming of owning this bike for many years, and when the chance presented itself I bit the bullet and bought one from a previous owner on eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pho Recipe</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/pho-recipe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/pho-recipe/</guid>
      <description>Friday night Pho is one of our house traditions. Nobody can resist the delicious combination of tastes that this simple Vietnamese noodle soup offers.
After years of eating pho, I finally decided to attempt making it for myself from scratch (or as from scratch as possible) purely as an exercise of appreciation for this noodle dish.
Recipe Like all &amp;ldquo;fancy&amp;rdquo; foods, pho comes from a humble origin: it was created originally as an easy way to use the parts of cattle that could not otherwise be sold: namely, the bones, tendons, and other bits of beef.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3D printers</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/3dprinting/3d-printers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/3dprinting/3d-printers/</guid>
      <description>During 2012, I had access to TechShop SF, a makerspace in San Francisco which is sadly now defunct, I took several courses that taught FDM 3D printing basics. This got me hooked on the idea of owning my own 3D printers. However, this wasn&amp;rsquo;t reasonable until around 2017 owing to market forces driving down the prices to less than £300 or $400 for a decent entry-level printer.
As of this writing, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the opportunity of owning and operating 3 different 3D printers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snapshot testing with Jest &#43; Preact &#43; Picostyle</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/snapshot-testing-with-preact-and-picostyle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/snapshot-testing-with-preact-and-picostyle/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been using Preact as my alternative (API compatible) React of choice for a few side projects for a while now, the main advantage being the API compatibility with a significantly smaller sized addition to dependencies.
Likewise, my favorite CSS-in-JS microlibrary: Picostyle has similar file-size advantages.
Micro-libraries are great because they are small enough to be able to dig into their source code quickly and make customizations.
Snapshot testing with Preact and Picostyle It&amp;rsquo;s not immediately obvious how to test Preact JSX within a Jest snapshot test, especially when they are styled with Picostyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KeyDings</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/keydings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/keydings/</guid>
      <description>As a way to learn the MacOS Cocoa API and Swift, I set out to write a MacOS system tray app that would provide IBM Model M &amp;ldquo;clicky&amp;rdquo; keyboard sound effects whenever the OS detected a key up or down event.
To my complete surprise I was able to get a functional app working within an afternoon, which goes to prove that the ecosystem for writing MacOS apps is well designed and mature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tabular / vertical code alignment in ES without IntelliJ</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/tabular-vertical-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/tabular-vertical-alignment/</guid>
      <description>While block indentation alignment (1) is enough for most people, I believe further alignment formatters, especially tabular or &amp;ldquo;vertical&amp;rdquo; alignment (2) tools, can greatly help in reducing the time it takes to visually process details in code:
// (1) const bike: Record&amp;lt;string|number&amp;gt; = { wheelSize: 16, topTubeLength: 24.5, manufacturer: &#39;Brompton&#39; }; // vs // (2) const bike: Record&amp;lt;string|number&amp;gt; = { wheelSize: 16, topTubeLength: 24.5, manufacturer: &#39;Brompton&#39; };  The code in (2) is much clearer in tabular form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CelCom: Feature Toggles and Testing</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/feature-toggles-and-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/feature-toggles-and-testing/</guid>
      <description>This post is a Celestial Combat devlog and also be found here.
Some of the code for Celestial Combat has been structured to provide a easy facility for switching major subsystems of the game on/off. Additionally, unit testing is not time-efficient given the benefits vs effort involved: we offer a cheaper solution in the form of scenario tests.
Feature toggles You have the option of toggling game functionality via the URL you use to access the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CelCom: Simplifying development tooling</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/tooling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/tooling/</guid>
      <description>This post is a Celestial Combat devlog and also be found here.
Writing code is a necessary evil to get things done on a project and often the best kind of code is no code at all. Good tooling helps us do things:
 FASTER: avoid writing code when the task least requires it CHEAPER: avoid writing code when results are not worth the effort EASIER: avoid barriers for contributors of all skill levels  Creating game art (EASIER) CelCom exclusively uses vector graphics, which is one of the simplest and most space-efficient ways to represent art in a game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding nostalgic music from 1996 Microsoft Interactive CD Sampler</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/microsoft-interactive-cd-sampler-music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/microsoft-interactive-cd-sampler-music/</guid>
      <description>In my childhood, I used to move around a lot. We usually didn&amp;rsquo;t have allowances for things that other kids used to hold onto, to be kept between moves. Instead I collected music files and other digital treasures that pleased my young brain.
One file that&amp;rsquo;s firmly stuck in my memory was theme music for the 1996 Microsoft Interactive CD Sampler main menu. I rediscovered it on YouTube recently and it sounds like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CelCom: Improving HUD indicator designs</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/hud-indicators/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/hud-indicators/</guid>
      <description>This post is a Celestial Combat devlog and also be found here.
Game design is essentially UX design. Bad experience design is more than jarring: it drives beginner players away. CelCom previously had an example of bad experience design in one of it core gameplay mechanics: landing spaceships was awkward and difficult. First you needed to be able to find the planet you want to land on, then you had to move to it, possibly avoiding other planets and stars en route.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CelCom: Implementing saved games</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/saved-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/celcom/saved-games/</guid>
      <description>This post is a Celestial Combat devlog and also be found here.
Celestial Combat is a game large in ambition and scope. Battles often span multiple solar systems with hundreds of spacecraft and planets with caches of materials for war production.
As the gameplay solidified, finding a way to persist player progress grew more important. Saving score and progress within a battle means players are likely to come back to the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brompton Wheel Veloplugs</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/brompton-veloplugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/brompton-veloplugs/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve used rim plugs (&amp;ldquo;Veloplug&amp;rdquo; is a brand of rim plug) in 3 separate bike builds and they have been worthwhile as a rim tape / strip alternative.
Essentially, rim plugs are drawing pin sized bits of plastic that have a tub instead of a solid rod which you insert into the spoke holes from the inside of the wheel.
Their purpose is to protect inner tubes (squishy rubber things that hold air) from the inside of the rim bed; the rim bed contains spoke holes drilled by a wheel rim factory that have rough edges, which may puncture inner tubes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bike Light Phone Mount</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-light-phone-mount/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-light-phone-mount/</guid>
      <description>Broken LED lights 2 years ago I bought two inexpensive LED bike lights which both ended up broken after some use. Since they were cheap but contained some salvageable parts I disassembled them to see what was wrong: power leads to the Li-ion cells had disconnected owing to a shoddy soldering job at the factory. However, after resoldering the leads, further testing showed that the cells had nearly completely died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Sound Tin</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/random-sound-tin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/random-sound-tin/</guid>
      <description>My daughter is approaching the 6 month mark. This is a time when kids start to develop gross motor skills and begin to express themselves through play. In anticipation, I jumped at the chance to make some dynamic toys for her in addition to the mostly rigid ones she&amp;rsquo;s collected so far.
  Ended up doing a Friday late night build. Since I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a collection of sounds ready, I just dumped all the sound effects from the DOS game Blood as a test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isle of Wight Randonnee 2018</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2018/</guid>
      <description>The IOW Randonnee was fantastic this year. I rode down from Euston again, but this time heading from Euston to Farnham and then bearing south towards Petersfield and finally to Portsmouth, rather than Southampton.
Euston to Portsmouth  https://www.strava.com/activities/1551615269

Cycle Island 2018  https://www.strava.com/activities/1554338241

Highlights  riding down to the coast to meet Brett shadowing the London Brompton Club riders pit-stop at the Sun Inn where I bit into venison sausage that still had buckshot in it the many hellos and morsels of conversations exchanged with random cyclists throughout the ride  The pacing was really good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Try before you buy fonts</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/try-before-you-buy-fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/try-before-you-buy-fonts/</guid>
      <description>A coding font called Dank Mono showed up in my programming feed recently. As someone who is always looking for ways to improve my coding environment, changing the default IDE font seemed like something worth investigating.
I was pretty happy with Iosevka already but was curious to see if Dank Mono was worth the social media hype; setting it as the IDE font would be the best way to judge its merits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samsung Gear 360 (SM-200) image and video workflow on MacOS</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/gear-360-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/gear-360-workflow/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve long been interested in 360 panoramic photos and videos and being a patient tech consumer, I was fortunate to get the 2016 Gear 360 camera for the low price of £80 shipped; 22% of the original launch price of £350.
Additionally, I wrote a simple 360 web viewer, so I can use any image host (e.g. Imgur, Dropbox, etc.) and not be tied to a specific online platform like Kuula.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gear VR Controller Reverse Engineering</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/gear-vr-rev-eng/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/gear-vr-rev-eng/</guid>
      <description>The result so far Here&amp;rsquo;s a video demo of I was able to achieve with this reverse engineering effort:
  Click here if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in running this yourself.
Background About a week ago I was having a look at some new input devices to use for my game experiments that were a little more interesting than a simple USB or Bluetooth Gamepad. As I kept a close eye on consumer VR technology in 2016&amp;frasl;2017, it occurred to me now that many of the devices released in the past year have been updated and on the market for at least a few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mocute Bluetooth Gamepads</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/mocute-bluetooth-gamepad/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/mocute-bluetooth-gamepad/</guid>
      <description>These cheap bluetooth gamepads are often branded and sold as remote shutter buttons for smartphones. I think their best purpose is actually to be used as gamepads, especially for mobile devices and bluetooth-enabled PCs. They can be routinely found on either eBay or Amazon for around $3 or 5 GBP, shipping included. This makes them one of the best value bluetooth input devices on the market as of 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faulty Raspberry Pi Zero W</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/guides/faulty-rpi0w/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/guides/faulty-rpi0w/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;ve done everything you&amp;rsquo;ve known how to get a Raspberry Pi Zero W (v1.1) to work but can&amp;rsquo;t get it to boot up and recognize the Wifi, there&amp;rsquo;s a chance you may have a defective board.
  Setup After purchasing you should have been able to do this to get it working:
 https://gist.github.com/gbaman/50b6cca61dd1c3f88f41 https://gist.github.com/gbaman/975e2db164b3ca2b51ae11e45e8fd40a https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xj3MPmJhAPU  Instead, research has led me to reach the same conclusions as these other people who have had the same issues with their RP0W</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modernizing a Moulton Automatic</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/moulton-automatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/moulton-automatic/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been obsessed with the design lineage of the Moulton bicycle ever since I got my first small wheeled folding bike: Bessie the Brompton. In mid-April 2017, a Moulton automatic appeared on eBay for 150 GBP with no bids and I decided I had to have it. I was the only bidder and minus another 60 GBP in shipping fees, it arrived at my doorstep from Stotfold, Bedfordshire.
When the courier arrived with it the first thing I noticed was that it was quite long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrimpy - the evolution of a tiny bike</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/shrimpy-bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/shrimpy-bike/</guid>
      <description>The base frame The foundation of the build was a tiny clown bike manufactured some time in the early 2000s under the name &amp;ldquo;Mikro-bike&amp;rdquo;. The marketing website from 2002, archived via WayBack Machine is available here. My particular bike came with a new seatpost and a worn rear wheel (solid rubber!) following years of enjoyment under its previous owner. It also had a coaster brake. The whole package was had for 30 GBP delivered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isle of Wight Randonnee 2017</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2017/</guid>
      <description>London Euston to Southampton, Cycle Island Tour Every year, the Isle of Wight hosts a cycling event which circumnavigates the island. As many of my friends in the various cycling groups I belong to were taking part in this event this year, it was only natural to join them on this unique free event. There were two routes: a 55 km and 100 km route. I thought I would do the longer route since I was still in the early stages of being acclimatized to long distances in the saddle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>suoman commute machine</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/suoman-commute-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/suoman-commute-machine/</guid>
      <description>A Budget single-speed build @suoman was having real issues with her 100 quid department store bike so I decided to chip in and get her something better especially after hearing how nice it would be to own a racing-style-not-so-heavy-bike.
I had a think and came up with a budget (&amp;lt; 120 GBP total) for her new ride. In addition to being as cheap as possible while being a decent bike, this new bike need to: - have better brakes than current bike - be more easily maintainable than current bike - be more lightweight than current bike - mount a rack for carrying panniers - look cooler - be more fun to ride</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polymer clay sculpting</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/polymer-clay-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/polymer-clay-2017/</guid>
      <description>Petite Little Red Riding Hood After building Del a red mini-velo (named Little Red Riding Hood) last year, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d follow it up with a smaller version of the small bike as a gift during our first clay session. Having purchased a heat gun recently, I experimented with baking the pieces individually on a low heat setting, then joining them with industrial strength cyanoacrylate super glue. Here&amp;rsquo;s how it turned out:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Norfolk Nobbler 2017</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/norfolk-nobbler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/norfolk-nobbler/</guid>
      <description>London to Cambridge to Hunstanton to King’s Lynn The first long ride of the year was done with the London Beer and Bike Group; leaving from Bernie Spains Gardens in Southwark, the route was to take us to Cambridge via the canal towpaths in the east end of London and through Ely onward to King’s Lynn and to the beach at Hunstanton.
 https://www.strava.com/activities/905771639 
New options for storage: Carradice SQR Trax A new piece of kit was mounted onto Bessie the Brompton for this route to see whether it was worthwhile having the extra carry capacity: the Carradice SQR Trax bag with SQR mount.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheap Bike Bell Modification</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-bell-mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-bell-mod/</guid>
      <description>Having bought a bell similar to this one quite a while back for roughly (5 GBP), I&amp;rsquo;d seen how well it worked very loudly and clearly as a bell. Unfortunately, using the bell as a handlebar attachment is less than stellar due to its flawed strap design:
The steel strap which comes with it, leaves a large gap and owing to that, the bell has a tendency to spin around when you hit the slightest of bumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manchester Critical Mass February 2017</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/mcr-critmass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/mcr-critmass/</guid>
      <description>I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been in town to join critical mass since moving to Manchester in Sept 2016. Finally free of obligations in London for the last Friday of the month, I decided to join fellow cyclists for Critical Mass.
I ordered some of these 10 meter LED fairy lights (7 GBP) off Amazon a while back for our flat and they were conveniently USB powered. This was perfect for wrapping Bessie the Brompton up in and for pooting around town (with many happy onlookers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Celestial Combat</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/games/celcom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/games/celcom/</guid>
      <description>Originally written as a way to experiment with vector graphics in PixiJS. It has since formed into a complete game. Celestial Combat is a game of galactic colonization, and conquest.
Excerpt from &amp;ldquo;How to play&amp;rdquo;  You begin with either an invasion fleet (1 x Fighter + 4 invasion Freighters) or a single occupied planet.
To colonize planets, you must land on them when they are unoccupied with your Fighter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Particle Tracks</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/particle-tracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/particle-tracks/</guid>
      <description> Wrote a little procedural art widget drawing inspiration from bubble / cloud chambers used to study particle trajectories. This toy makes use of the excellent scrubbing dat.GUI library to change initial values.
  Live play  Source code </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PewPew.js</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/pewpew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/pewpew/</guid>
      <description> I wrote this toy during a particularly long and unproductive meeting that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t leave. Turn almost any web page into a shooting gallery with a click of a button.
  Source code </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/cellular-automata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/cellular-automata/</guid>
      <description>This is a toy script that generates a random 2D celluar automata ruleset and applies it to a randomly generated world with each run of the web page. You can click on the viewport to reset it with a completely different universe, starting population and rules for the universe.
 Some universes are more stable than others, which may last for only a few cycles before all the cells die off.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Spirit Single-Speed Conversion</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/free-spirit-single-speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/free-spirit-single-speed/</guid>
      <description>My parents purchased a pair of old road bikes from the mid/late 70s in relatively good condition for their age before the family moved to Toronto (around 2011). The bikes were both &amp;ldquo;Free Spirit&amp;rdquo; branded machines that were apparently sold as lower-end bike shop bikes rather than department store bikes: they were relatively well built and had good components fitted to them.
I believe my mom got them both for $50 CAD at the time, which is quite a bargain!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dahon Classic V</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-classic-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-classic-v/</guid>
      <description>First released to the public in 1982, it came in single-speed, 3-speed internal gear hub (IGH), and 5-speed derailleur options. Having the smallest fold in a production bike at affordable prices, it became an instant consumer hit. The original design itself lived on for a number of years into the 90s.
  Before 1
      Before 2
      Chainring size</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GPXMapFactor</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/gpx-mapfactor/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/gpx-mapfactor/</guid>
      <description>Route-Importer for MapFactor doesn&amp;#39;t work :( Have to write my own...
&amp;mdash; Jim (@spacefishing) June 30, 2016  
Wrote a small tool to convert and insert waypoints from a GPX route into a MapFactor Navigator route.
MapFactor Navigator is an offline turn-by-turn navigation program you can stick on your phone. Was going to cycle from Leicester to Cardiff on Friday but instead got really sick and wrote this program.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London-Cambridge-Leicester</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-cambridge-leicester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-cambridge-leicester/</guid>
      <description>Inbound to Cambridge from London We started off at city hall as an FW-club ride. And took one of the more direct and least elevated routes to Cambridge. Stopped 30 km short of Cambridge for lunch and a pint at a local pub. When the group got in, they settled into their YHA rooms and I checked in at my AirBnb. A pleasant ride especially after the late night on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipment Upgrades</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/equipment-upgrades-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/equipment-upgrades-2/</guid>
      <description>Upgrades to Bessie the Brompton Getting a Brompton brought me into whole new level of cycling. When I first got Bessie (the Brompton), the first thing I noticed was how little bike there was compared to how fast it could pick up speed. It was the next best thing to having a personal jetpack.
You see less of the bike in the cockpit. You feel less of the bike because a Brompton&amp;rsquo;s center of mass is lower, and you accelerate much much faster owing to the interplay between its smaller wheel size (16&amp;rdquo; x 3&amp;frasl;8&amp;rdquo;) and a higher gear ratio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Del&#39;s Red Minivelo</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dels-red-minivelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dels-red-minivelo/</guid>
      <description>A minivelo is a type of small wheeled bike with a standard road bike geometry and smaller sized wheels. Typically, they are non-folding and fill a niche in between full-sized road / city bikes and folding bikes. Simplicity is the order of the day with most minivelo designs.
I spent some time back in Canada in spring of 2016 and wanted a bike project with which I could surprise my wife (then girlfriend).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Slackson bot</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/slackson/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/slackson/</guid>
      <description>I wrote a Slack bot that controls and reacts to the state of Sonos controllers on your network. It can send GIPHYs to the channel as well as analyze the sentiment of the lyrics of the current song.
 jim [5:35 PM] whats playing sonosbot BOT [5:35 PM] `The Avener &amp;amp; Phoebe Killdeer - Fade Out Lines - The Avener Rework` jim [5:35 PM] pause sonosbot BOT [5:35 PM] `jim requested to pause this track.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycling in 2015</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/cycling-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/cycling-2015/</guid>
      <description>Biking since moving to London UK Cycling has always been a way for me to get around and explore places nearby but out of walking distance. After I moved to London, the first few weeks were fairly boring in spite of the extensive means of public transit offered by the city. City-hire bikes were available but they are not exactly enjoyable to ride.
I held off from buying a bike straight away because it was quite expensive to purchase a cycle in London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translucify</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/translucify/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/translucify/</guid>
      <description>Originally posted to https://medium.com/this-place/translucify-374ec3f621c5
Translucify is a drop-in solution for mismatched background colors between a web page and its images.
Highlights  Approximately 230 SLOC (source lines of code) No dependencies  The Why A classic way of improving the readability of a table with lots of rows is to set slightly different background colors for alternating rows. This all works nicely when you’re in control of the content that lives inside a row but what happens when the row has to show a thumbnail in one of its cells?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Mazes</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/maze/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/maze/</guid>
      <description>Mazes have always fasincated me. They can be generated via some simple rules and take beautiful, myriad forms.
New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve 2014 Maze Maze generator remixed! New years message written for friends for 2014.
 source code  Maze generator using the &amp;lt;table&amp;gt; element  Maze generator toy that draws mazes with tables and CSS-borders instead of canvas: runs in IE and also quite well on the Kindle experimental browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ColorRun.pl bot</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/colorrunbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/colorrunbot/</guid>
      <description>A regular lurker on the /r/WebGames subreddit, I found a perfect game to write a 15 minute bot for a game posted that was posted.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London to Brighton Ride</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-to-brighton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-to-brighton/</guid>
      <description>First long ride (~100 km) from London to Brighton after getting the 100GBP Argos &amp;ldquo;crusader&amp;rdquo; bike. We tried following a basic Google mapped route but weren&amp;rsquo;t used to the roundabouts. Almost ended up on an M series highway for one of the turns. And I learned the importance of continuously eating on a long distance bike ride. Felt a bit faint before Ditchling; blood sugar was low.
  Brighton 1</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foldable rowboat v1</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/foldable-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/foldable-boat/</guid>
      <description>Over the summer of 2013 several very well made corrugated plastic boats were featured on DIY sites and on r/buildaboat. It all seemed very simple to do and I&amp;rsquo;d always wanted my own boat to fool around with so I thought why not! Corrugated plastic in large sheets were easy to come by once a little research had been done and the only other materials which were required were reusable zip-ties and some kind of propulsion device: a paddle or a small trolling motor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev Weekend 3</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/games/gdw3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/games/gdw3/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Fisches&amp;rdquo; For the 3rd gamedev weekend project, I chose to take part in a game jam. The theme was set as anything related to &amp;ldquo;fishing&amp;rdquo;.
I had grandiose visions for this game, but sadly the scope of that meant it would never be finished without burn out. Written in Coffeescript, but has since been ported over to JS. I drew all the graphics on a Samsung Galaxy Note 10.1 and resampled some public domain / royalty-free sounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev Weekend 2</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/games/gdw2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/games/gdw2/</guid>
      <description>My second gamedev weekend project, this time I attempted to create a web version of a popular board game: Kulami.
Development finished on 30/05/2013. Current version has been patched to run in modern browsers (WebAudio API was changed since 2013).
Original features: - an intermediate skill-level AI player with taunts (filthy meatbag!) - RANDOM or a completely user-defined board layout - final score breakdown
Play it now  How to play Construct board layout Drag the tiles to form a board of non-overlapping tiles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gamedev Weekend 1</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/games/gdw1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/games/gdw1/</guid>
      <description>Junior&amp;rsquo;s first 48 hour collaborative gamedev Life gets boring sometimes when you do the same thing over and over again by yourself. Two weeks ago, I had an epiphany: I didn&amp;rsquo;t have to do the same thing by myself if there were people I could coax into doing it with me. Must have been what I&amp;rsquo;d missed out on all this time.
Finding people was easy enough: I scrounged 30 seconds of my day and put up a Facebook status update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TechShop notes</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/repairs/notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Dec 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/repairs/notes/</guid>
      <description>Various tidbits learned from SF TechShop classes Oxy-Acetylene Torch Starting: Open the acetylene valve to the torch first, then the oxygen valve.
Stopping: Close the oxygen valve, then the acetylene.
Gas valve open/close order mnemonic: POOP &amp;mdash; Propane, Oxygen, Oxygen, Propane.
Oxygen blown by the cutting head of the torch actually burns the steel / iron which is being cut. The extra oxygen combusts the material which turns into slag (~oxide) falling off onto the floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raygun</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/raygun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/raygun/</guid>
      <description>Laser shooting prop gun After finishing a few basic machining courses, I was very much tempted to explore inventing and making something which was not a test weld or a simple bottle opener from 18 gauge mild steel. Enter the raygun shooting saloon. Initial morsels of the idea were inspired by a few prior instances of this laser toy that are scattered throughout the Internet.
As most of the actual complexity lay in the programming of the microcontroller to poll for laser hits on the target, it was only natural to use this as my first actual machined project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sculpting in 2012, 2013</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/sculpting-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/sculpting-2013/</guid>
      <description>Starman &amp;amp; Crashed UFO late 2012
  Starman1
      Starman2
      Starman3
     A ceramic homage to Earthbound created as part of a ceramics course. The starman&amp;rsquo;s insignia is glazed in black. Its outer coat is spray painted with silver metallic paint.
Instamorph T-Rex Skull August 2013
  Trex1
      Trex2</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TSP Solver</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/traveling-salesman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/traveling-salesman/</guid>
      <description>The travelling salesman problem (TSP) asks the following question: &amp;ldquo;Given a list of cities and the distances between each pair of cities, what is the shortest possible route that visits each city exactly once and returns to the origin city?&amp;rdquo; It is an NP-hard problem in combinatorial optimization, important in operations research and theoretical computer science.
 Iteratively solving the Travelling Salesman problem with k-opt operations Fast operations such as 2-Opt are less computationally expensive, but due to granularity, more likely to become stuck in local extrema.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textured 3D tunnel</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/tunnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/tunnel/</guid>
      <description>I spent a weekend night implementing an old demoscene 3D tunnel rendering trick in HTML5, here are the results:
Textured, shaded, ray casting rendering of a tunnel. Camera is free to rotate, pan and change focal length. Controls: W + mouse look A S D    Source code See code on Github</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Road signs</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/road-signs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/road-signs/</guid>
      <description>This was an undergraduate computer vision extra-curricular project.
Image segmentation goal: finding text within am image of a road sign The growing abilities of video feed APIs allow for mobile and domain-specific programs that were previously out of reach. One application that I had in mind was video frame text extraction, which itself could be the foundation for magnification or text-to-speech capability that could aid the visually impaired, translation for foreign language signs and contextual advertising services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GMBrowser</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/tools/gmbrowser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Oct 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/tools/gmbrowser/</guid>
      <description>Cache Google Maps tiles by browsing the location of interest This is simple C app that I wrote up and tested in about 2 hours that automatically saves the map tiles of Google Maps as you browse a location of interest. The bundled tool, tiler is a handy utility for arranging the matrix of the gathered Google Maps tiles for a certain zoom level.
Originally this was written as a fast and dirty way to get lots of map data for an independent project in the summer of 2009.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM M2 Clicky Keyboard Repair</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/repairs/m2kb/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2009 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/repairs/m2kb/</guid>
      <description>These particular model M buckling spring (B-S) or &amp;ldquo;clicky&amp;rdquo; keyboards were paired and sold with IBM PS/1 and some PS/2 systems circa 1990. As of writing, my M2 keyboard is about 18 years old. Old age brings about hardware failures of all sorts and the M2 is no exception. The most common, non-mechanical, failure people have encountered have been dead keyboard controller boards.
When plugged into a PS/2 keyboard port, the M2 shows CapsLock and Scroll Lock lights on but is irresponsive after POST (Power On System Test).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DOM-based RTS Engine</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/games/jscc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/games/jscc/</guid>
      <description>A Command and Conquer engine in JS Update Nov. 2011:
Aditya Ravi Shankar created a version that uses canvas blitting instead of DOM manipulation.
 Your unfinished C&amp;amp;C demo inspired me to give it a shot. My version uses HTML5/Canvas and works in Chrome/Firefox.
  http://www.adityaravishankar.com/projects/games/command-and-conquer/
 http://www.adityaravishankar.com/2011/11/command-and-conquer-programming-an-rts-game-in-html5-and-javascript/
  This was a very ambitious project to fully recreate the first C&amp;amp;C game and introduce in-game objects for expansion by user scripting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flash games</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/games/flash-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Feb 2004 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/games/flash-games/</guid>
      <description>Wrote and animated a lot of Flash games/animations back in the early 2000s during my time in high-school. Here are a sample of some of the better ones.
Defend 2 - Super Tank (2004) 
Controls  WASD to move the tank mouse to aim, click to fire SPACE to switch weapons  Base Attack - 2D War Simulator (2002) This was sort of half-way between a game and screen-saver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 1000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/about/</guid>
      <description>jsyang.ca is a software engineering + management consultant currently living in Manchester, UK.
Want to hire me? Head over to cohesive.dev.
This site was generated with Hugo with a customized yinyang theme.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>