<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyclings on jsyang.ca</title>
    <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cyclings on jsyang.ca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jsyang.ca/cycling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dahon PrestoLite - The Lightest 16&#34; Wheeler Yet</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-prestolite/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-prestolite/</guid>
      <description>The Dahon PrestoLite is a 16&amp;rdquo; (ETRTO 305mm) wheeled folding bike with the geometry of a Moulton Mk3 constructed mainly out of aluminium. I&amp;rsquo;ve lusted after a Moulton Mk3 for a while but the small apartment where we live didn&amp;rsquo;t have the storage space for yet another non-folding bike; regardless of how small the wheels were.
  0th
      1st
      2nd</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jersey on a Pacific CarryMe</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/jersey-on-a-pacific-carryme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/jersey-on-a-pacific-carryme/</guid>
      <description>Jersey the Channel Island Jersey is the largest of the Channel Islands, located in the English Channel between England and France (but closer to France). As a dependency, but not formally a part of the United Kingdom, it has a mix of British and French cultures. With both English, and French being official languages, it was the only place outside of Canada I&amp;rsquo;ve travelled to with this specific combination of dual language road signage!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific CarryMe Shakedown Cruise</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme-shakedown-cruise/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme-shakedown-cruise/</guid>
      <description>The Chorlton Wanderers are a local social cycling group riding out of Chorlton Water Park, who do a social ride once a month. Given that the August 2019 ride was relatively flat and short (~60km), I decided to attempt it on the Pacific CarryMe to see what riding it for more than 10km was like in terms of pacing, fit, and to generally gauge the fun level.
It was the first shakedown cruise of the Pacific CarryMe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific CarryMe Folding Bike</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/pacific-carryme/</guid>
      <description>The CarryMe is a folding bike with an incredibly small wheel size of 8 inches manufactured by Pacific Cycles. The main advantage is its folding style which seeks to balance a stick-shaped fold while maintaining the ergonomics of a regular bike.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been dreaming of owning this bike for many years, and when the chance presented itself I bit the bullet and bought one from a previous owner on eBay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isle of Wight Randonnee 2018</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2018/</guid>
      <description>The IOW Randonnee was fantastic this year. I rode down from Euston again, but this time heading from Euston to Farnham and then bearing south towards Petersfield and finally to Portsmouth, rather than Southampton.
Euston to Portsmouth  https://www.strava.com/activities/1551615269

Cycle Island 2018  https://www.strava.com/activities/1554338241

Highlights  riding down to the coast to meet Brett shadowing the London Brompton Club riders pit-stop at the Sun Inn where I bit into venison sausage that still had buckshot in it the many hellos and morsels of conversations exchanged with random cyclists throughout the ride  The pacing was really good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modernizing a Moulton Automatic</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/moulton-automatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/moulton-automatic/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been obsessed with the design lineage of the Moulton bicycle ever since I got my first small wheeled folding bike: Bessie the Brompton. In mid-April 2017, a Moulton automatic appeared on eBay for 150 GBP with no bids and I decided I had to have it. I was the only bidder and minus another 60 GBP in shipping fees, it arrived at my doorstep from Stotfold, Bedfordshire.
When the courier arrived with it the first thing I noticed was that it was quite long.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shrimpy - the evolution of a tiny bike</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/shrimpy-bike/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/shrimpy-bike/</guid>
      <description>The base frame The foundation of the build was a tiny clown bike manufactured some time in the early 2000s under the name &amp;ldquo;Mikro-bike&amp;rdquo;. The marketing website from 2002, archived via WayBack Machine is available here. My particular bike came with a new seatpost and a worn rear wheel (solid rubber!) following years of enjoyment under its previous owner. It also had a coaster brake. The whole package was had for 30 GBP delivered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Isle of Wight Randonnee 2017</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/iow-2017/</guid>
      <description>London Euston to Southampton, Cycle Island Tour Every year, the Isle of Wight hosts a cycling event which circumnavigates the island. As many of my friends in the various cycling groups I belong to were taking part in this event this year, it was only natural to join them on this unique free event. There were two routes: a 55 km and 100 km route. I thought I would do the longer route since I was still in the early stages of being acclimatized to long distances in the saddle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>suoman commute machine</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/suoman-commute-machine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/suoman-commute-machine/</guid>
      <description>A Budget single-speed build @suoman was having real issues with her 100 quid department store bike so I decided to chip in and get her something better especially after hearing how nice it would be to own a racing-style-not-so-heavy-bike.
I had a think and came up with a budget (&amp;lt; 120 GBP total) for her new ride. In addition to being as cheap as possible while being a decent bike, this new bike need to: - have better brakes than current bike - be more easily maintainable than current bike - be more lightweight than current bike - mount a rack for carrying panniers - look cooler - be more fun to ride</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Norfolk Nobbler 2017</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/norfolk-nobbler/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/norfolk-nobbler/</guid>
      <description>London to Cambridge to Hunstanton to King’s Lynn The first long ride of the year was done with the London Beer and Bike Group; leaving from Bernie Spains Gardens in Southwark, the route was to take us to Cambridge via the canal towpaths in the east end of London and through Ely onward to King’s Lynn and to the beach at Hunstanton.
 https://www.strava.com/activities/905771639 
New options for storage: Carradice SQR Trax A new piece of kit was mounted onto Bessie the Brompton for this route to see whether it was worthwhile having the extra carry capacity: the Carradice SQR Trax bag with SQR mount.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manchester Critical Mass February 2017</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/mcr-critmass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/mcr-critmass/</guid>
      <description>I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been in town to join critical mass since moving to Manchester in Sept 2016. Finally free of obligations in London for the last Friday of the month, I decided to join fellow cyclists for Critical Mass.
I ordered some of these 10 meter LED fairy lights (7 GBP) off Amazon a while back for our flat and they were conveniently USB powered. This was perfect for wrapping Bessie the Brompton up in and for pooting around town (with many happy onlookers!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Free Spirit Single-Speed Conversion</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/free-spirit-single-speed/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/free-spirit-single-speed/</guid>
      <description>My parents purchased a pair of old road bikes from the mid/late 70s in relatively good condition for their age before the family moved to Toronto (around 2011). The bikes were both &amp;ldquo;Free Spirit&amp;rdquo; branded machines that were apparently sold as lower-end bike shop bikes rather than department store bikes: they were relatively well built and had good components fitted to them.
I believe my mom got them both for $50 CAD at the time, which is quite a bargain!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dahon Classic V</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-classic-v/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dahon-classic-v/</guid>
      <description>First released to the public in 1982, it came in single-speed, 3-speed internal gear hub (IGH), and 5-speed derailleur options. Having the smallest fold in a production bike at affordable prices, it became an instant consumer hit. The original design itself lived on for a number of years into the 90s.
  Before 1
      Before 2
      Chainring size</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London-Cambridge-Leicester</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-cambridge-leicester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-cambridge-leicester/</guid>
      <description>Inbound to Cambridge from London We started off at city hall as an FW-club ride. And took one of the more direct and least elevated routes to Cambridge. Stopped 30 km short of Cambridge for lunch and a pint at a local pub. When the group got in, they settled into their YHA rooms and I checked in at my AirBnb. A pleasant ride especially after the late night on Friday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Equipment Upgrades</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/equipment-upgrades-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/equipment-upgrades-2/</guid>
      <description>Upgrades to Bessie the Brompton Getting a Brompton brought me into whole new level of cycling. When I first got Bessie (the Brompton), the first thing I noticed was how little bike there was compared to how fast it could pick up speed. It was the next best thing to having a personal jetpack.
You see less of the bike in the cockpit. You feel less of the bike because a Brompton&amp;rsquo;s center of mass is lower, and you accelerate much much faster owing to the interplay between its smaller wheel size (16&amp;rdquo; x 3&amp;frasl;8&amp;rdquo;) and a higher gear ratio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Del&#39;s Red Minivelo</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dels-red-minivelo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/dels-red-minivelo/</guid>
      <description>A minivelo is a type of small wheeled bike with a standard road bike geometry and smaller sized wheels. Typically, they are non-folding and fill a niche in between full-sized road / city bikes and folding bikes. Simplicity is the order of the day with most minivelo designs.
I spent some time back in Canada in spring of 2016 and wanted a bike project with which I could surprise my wife (then girlfriend).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cycling in 2015</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/cycling-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/cycling-2015/</guid>
      <description>Biking since moving to London UK Cycling has always been a way for me to get around and explore places nearby but out of walking distance. After I moved to London, the first few weeks were fairly boring in spite of the extensive means of public transit offered by the city. City-hire bikes were available but they are not exactly enjoyable to ride.
I held off from buying a bike straight away because it was quite expensive to purchase a cycle in London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>London to Brighton Ride</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-to-brighton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/cycling/london-to-brighton/</guid>
      <description>First long ride (~100 km) from London to Brighton after getting the 100GBP Argos &amp;ldquo;crusader&amp;rdquo; bike. We tried following a basic Google mapped route but weren&amp;rsquo;t used to the roundabouts. Almost ended up on an M series highway for one of the turns. And I learned the importance of continuously eating on a long distance bike ride. Felt a bit faint before Ditchling; blood sugar was low.
  Brighton 1</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>