<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Arts on jsyang.ca</title>
    <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Arts on jsyang.ca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jsyang.ca/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>WormForm - a Typography Block Sandbox</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/wormform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/wormform/</guid>
      <description>The name comes from the first thing I tried to recreate within it: the NASA worm logo.
There&amp;rsquo;s a Twitter account I follow which often posts design-related inspiration and imagery from various books, artists, and commercial products: @presentcorrect. I happened upon a post that caught my eye. It was this page from the Gujarati Type Foundry Book (1940):
I knew I had to put something together to play with this system that laid out as pieces of multi-language typefaces with simple geometric shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Halloween Pumpkin Carving 2020</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/halloween-pumpkin-carving-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/halloween-pumpkin-carving-2020/</guid>
      <description>Pandemic lockdown had most of the neighborhood occupied with indoor activities this year. In our apartment block, we helped organize a pumpkin carving contest after visiting a local farm shop and getting a &amp;ldquo;standard&amp;rdquo; sized pumpkin for everyone in the block. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve carved a pumpkin, though it would be the first time I&amp;rsquo;d put any artistic effort into it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Polymer clay sculpting</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/polymer-clay-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/polymer-clay-2017/</guid>
      <description>Petite Little Red Riding Hood After building Del a red mini-velo (named Little Red Riding Hood) last year, I thought I&amp;rsquo;d follow it up with a smaller version of the small bike as a gift during our first clay session. Having purchased a heat gun recently, I experimented with baking the pieces individually on a low heat setting, then joining them with industrial strength cyanoacrylate super glue.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Particle Tracks</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/particle-tracks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/particle-tracks/</guid>
      <description>Wrote a little procedural art widget drawing inspiration from bubble / cloud chambers used to study particle trajectories. This toy makes use of the excellent scrubbing dat.GUI library to change initial values.
  Live play  Source code </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PewPew.js</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/pewpew/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/pewpew/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this toy during a particularly long and unproductive meeting that I couldn&amp;rsquo;t leave. Turn almost any web page into a shooting gallery with a click of a button.
  Source code </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Cellular Automata</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/cellular-automata/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/cellular-automata/</guid>
      <description>This is a toy script that generates a random 2D celluar automata ruleset and applies it to a randomly generated world with each run of the web page. You can click on the viewport to reset it with a completely different universe, starting population and rules for the universe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative Mazes</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/maze/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/maze/</guid>
      <description>Mazes have always fasincated me. They can be generated via some simple rules and take beautiful, myriad forms.
New Year&amp;rsquo;s Eve 2014 Maze Maze generator remixed! New years message written for friends for 2014.
 source code  Maze generator using the &amp;lt;table&amp;gt; element  Maze generator toy that draws mazes with tables and CSS-borders instead of canvas: runs in IE and also quite well on the Kindle experimental browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Raygun</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/raygun/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/raygun/</guid>
      <description>Laser shooting prop gun After finishing a few basic machining courses, I was very much tempted to explore inventing and making something which was not a test weld or a simple bottle opener from 18 gauge mild steel. Enter the raygun shooting saloon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sculpting in 2012, 2013</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/sculpting-2013/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/sculpting-2013/</guid>
      <description>Starman &amp;amp; Crashed UFO late 2012
  Starman1
      Starman2
      Starman3
     A ceramic homage to Earthbound created as part of a ceramics course. The starman&amp;rsquo;s insignia is glazed in black.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Textured 3D tunnel</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/art/tunnel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/art/tunnel/</guid>
      <description>I spent a weekend night implementing an old demoscene 3D tunnel rendering trick in HTML5, here are the results:
Textured, shaded, ray casting rendering of a tunnel. Camera is free to rotate, pan and change focal length. Controls: W + mouse look A S D    Source code See code on Github</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
