<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hardwares on jsyang.ca</title>
    <link>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hardwares on jsyang.ca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://jsyang.ca/hardware/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Franklin BOOKMAN Data Archive</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/franklin-electronics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/franklin-electronics/</guid>
      <description>The Bookman Archive has moved to BookmanArchive.com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dell NavTeq BT-332 Bluetooth GPS Receiver</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/navteq-bt332-bluetooth-gps-receiver/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/navteq-bt332-bluetooth-gps-receiver/</guid>
      <description>As part of a Dell Axim PDA bundle, I came into possession of this curious Dell Navteq BT-332 Bluetooth GPS Receiver that I&amp;rsquo;m planning to use with an offline OSM app on a laptop (something normally without a location sensor).
Before phones and other devices integrated location sensors the common setup was having an external GPS receiver that would process and relay location data via Bluetooth or physically connected serial (RS-232) port.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Think Outside Bluetooth Folding Keyboard</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/think-outside-bluetooth-folding-keyboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/think-outside-bluetooth-folding-keyboard/</guid>
      <description>When the local coronavirus restrictions were enacted early on this year, I was determined not to let this time go to waste. The idea: read more and improve my writing by removing distractions where possible. Distraction-free writing (post coming soon) and other activities of this sort require a lot of forethought and set-up to have a chance at consistent success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Guitar Hero Live Bluetooth Controller Poll Rate Testing Jig</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/ghlive-controller-rate-testing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hardware/ghlive-controller-rate-testing/</guid>
      <description>After releasing the GHLiveBLE tool, there were a number of hardcore Clone Hero enthusiasts who were curious to find out the poll rate of the GHLive bluetooth guitar controller. Given that the poll rate being how fast the controller can register button presses to the computer, a higher rate would allow for more &amp;ldquo;precise&amp;rdquo; play for the dedicated rhythm game fans.
And so, I set out to find the limits of the Guitar Hero Live hardware.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
