<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hacks on jsyang.ca</title>
    <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hacks on jsyang.ca</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://jsyang.ca/hacks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guitar Hero Live Bluetooth controller</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/ghliveble/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/ghliveble/</guid>
      <description>Ever since we visited the National Videogame Museum, my wife and I got more and more into Guitar Hero style rhythm games. Late last year, I did some research and found a great open source project called Clone Hero which aims to vastly improve upon games of this genre.
For her birthday, I got an XBox360 version of the Guitar Hero Live controller which is meant to work with Windows PCs though with a steps of complicated set up before we could play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brompton Wheel Veloplugs</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/brompton-veloplugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/brompton-veloplugs/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve used rim plugs (&amp;ldquo;Veloplug&amp;rdquo; is a brand of rim plug) in 3 separate bike builds and they have been worthwhile as a rim tape / strip alternative.
Essentially, rim plugs are drawing pin sized bits of plastic that have a tub instead of a solid rod which you insert into the spoke holes from the inside of the wheel.
Their purpose is to protect inner tubes (squishy rubber things that hold air) from the inside of the rim bed; the rim bed contains spoke holes drilled by a wheel rim factory that have rough edges, which may puncture inner tubes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bike Light Phone Mount</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-light-phone-mount/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-light-phone-mount/</guid>
      <description>Broken LED lights 2 years ago I bought two inexpensive LED bike lights which both ended up broken after some use. Since they were cheap but contained some salvageable parts I disassembled them to see what was wrong: power leads to the Li-ion cells had disconnected owing to a shoddy soldering job at the factory. However, after resoldering the leads, further testing showed that the cells had nearly completely died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Sound Tin</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/random-sound-tin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/random-sound-tin/</guid>
      <description>My daughter is approaching the 6 month mark. This is a time when kids start to develop gross motor skills and begin to express themselves through play. In anticipation, I jumped at the chance to make some dynamic toys for her in addition to the mostly rigid ones she&amp;rsquo;s collected so far.
  Ended up doing a Friday late night build. Since I didn&amp;rsquo;t have a collection of sounds ready, I just dumped all the sound effects from the DOS game Blood as a test.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gear VR Controller Reverse Engineering</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/gear-vr-rev-eng/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/gear-vr-rev-eng/</guid>
      <description>The result so far Here&amp;rsquo;s a video demo of I was able to achieve with this reverse engineering effort:
  Click here if you&amp;rsquo;re interested in running this yourself.
Background About a week ago I was having a look at some new input devices to use for my game experiments that were a little more interesting than a simple USB or Bluetooth Gamepad. As I kept a close eye on consumer VR technology in 2016&amp;frasl;2017, it occurred to me now that many of the devices released in the past year have been updated and on the market for at least a few months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cheap Bike Bell Modification</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-bell-mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/bike-bell-mod/</guid>
      <description>Having bought a bell similar to this one quite a while back for roughly (5 GBP), I&amp;rsquo;d seen how well it worked very loudly and clearly as a bell. Unfortunately, using the bell as a handlebar attachment is less than stellar due to its flawed strap design:
The steel strap which comes with it, leaves a large gap and owing to that, the bell has a tendency to spin around when you hit the slightest of bumps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foldable rowboat v1</title>
      <link>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/foldable-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://jsyang.ca/hacks/foldable-boat/</guid>
      <description>Over the summer of 2013 several very well made corrugated plastic boats were featured on DIY sites and on r/buildaboat. It all seemed very simple to do and I&amp;rsquo;d always wanted my own boat to fool around with so I thought why not! Corrugated plastic in large sheets were easy to come by once a little research had been done and the only other materials which were required were reusable zip-ties and some kind of propulsion device: a paddle or a small trolling motor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>